[{"id": 2822, "question": "Martha had been working for Miller Laboratories for two years, but she was not happy there. Nothing significant had happened in the way of promotions or salary increases. Martha felt that her supervisor, a younger and less experienced person than she, did not like her. In fact, the supervisor often said unpleasant things to her. One day, while talking with her friend Maria, she mentioned how discouraged she was. Maria gave her the name of a cousin of hers who was director of Human Resources Department for a large chemical company. Martha called him the next day and set up an interview on her lunch hour. During the interview, Mr. Petri said, \"You're just the kind of person we need here. You're being wasted in your other job. Give me a call in a day or two. I'm sure we can find a place for y...\n\nQ: Martha is unhappy in her job because    _   .", "options": ["she has not advanced", "the work is not significant", "her supervisor is younger than she", "there is too much work with little payment"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 603, "question": "STRANGERS parties go wild these days. The main idea of them is to never let the people know who their matches are until the last minute. These are some popular practices that are storming the world's youth on this V-day. Speed dating It's exactly what the name implies. Complete with a timer, a whistle and 50 willing singles, speed dating is not the traditional dinner and a movie type of first date. Singles pay US $35 for three minutes with more than two dozen future dates. They ask questions and try to get to know each other. At the sound of a whistle, they do the same thing all over again--25 times in all. Lock and key party Women are given a lock and men are given a key, upon arriving at the party. Each key and lock has several matches. One can hunt for his/her later-to-be sweetheart in ...\n\nQ: How many of the parties offer gifts or prizes?", "options": ["1.", "2.", "3.", "4."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2362, "question": "No one wants to look stupid or do the wrong thing at a new job. It is important to make the right impression from the very first day. You will face new people. You will be in a new place. It may be difficult to know what to do. Here are five tips to help you make it through the first days at a new job: 1. First impressions can last forever. Make sure you make a good one. Before your first day, find out if your new job has a dress code (rules about what you can wear to work). If so, be sure to follow it. No matter what, always be neat and clean. 2. Get to work on time. 3. Pay attention to introductions. One of the first things that your supervisor may do is to introduce you to co-workers. These co-workers will be important to you. They are the ones who will answer your questions when the bo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["You should be the first one to arrive at work.", "You should ask your co-workers about your duties.", "You should not be eager to go back home after work.", "You are required to arrive 15 minutes earlier"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 936, "question": "When she looked ahead, Florence Chadwick saw nothing but a solid wall of fog. Her body was numb .She had been swimming for nearly sixteen hours. Already she was the first woman to swim the English Channel in both directions. Now, at age 34,her goal was to become the first woman to swim from Catalina Island to the California coast. On that fourth of July morning in 1952,the sea was like an ice bath and the fog was so thick that she could hardly see her support boats. Sharks swam toward her lone figure, only to be driven away by rifle shots. Against the frigid grip of the sea, she struggled on--hour after hour--while millions watched on national television. Alongside Florence in one of the boats , her mother and her trainer offered encouragement. They told her it wasn't much farther. But all...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": [".Florence Chadwick spent less time swimming across the Catalina Channel than men.", ".Florence Chadwick succeeded in swimming across the Catalina Channel in September,1952.", "People had to use guns to drive away some flesh-eating animals in the sea.", ".No women but Florence Chadwick were able to swim the English Channel in both directions."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2279, "question": "It was 1961 and I was in the fifth grade. My marks in school were miserable and, the thing was, I didn't know enough to really care. My older bother and I lived with Mom in an ugly multi-family house in Detroit. We watched TV every night. The background noise of our lives was gunfire and horses' hoofs from \"Wagon Train\" or \"Cheyenne\", and laughter from\"I Love Lucy\", or\"Mister Ed\".After supper, we'd lie on Mom's bed and stare for hours at the TV screen. But one day Mom changed our world forever. She turned off the TV. Our mother had only been able to get through third grade. But, she was much brighter and smarter than we boys know at the time. She had noticed something in the suburban houses where she cleaned books. So she came home one day, switched off the TV, sat us down and explained th...\n\nQ: How did the two boys feel about going to the library at first?", "options": ["They were afraid", "They were reluctant.", "They were impatient.", "They were eager to go."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1660, "question": "About 10 years ago, I started a job as a trainer for a telemarketing agency.In one of my first classes, the head trainer told a very inspiring story. He began by drawing a stickman standing in the middle of a circle.To make it more interesting, he drew things like a house, a car, and a few friends inside the circle. He asked the question, \"Can anyone tell me what this is?\" In a long silence, one guy decided to throw out \"the world?\" The trainer said, \"That's close and this is your Comfort Zone.Inside your circle you have all the things that are important to you.\" \"Your home, your family, your friends, and your job.People feel that inside this circle they are safe from any danger or conflict.\" \"Can anyone tell me what happens when you step out of this circle?\" A strong silence came over the...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the Comfort Zone is   _  .", "options": ["a place where we can enjoy a lot of amusement", "a person who can offer us some comfort and protect us", "a state in which we feel all safe and right with the world", "a circle which we don't dare to get out of"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1276, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is most probably the writer's problem as a new teacher?", "options": ["She didn't like teaching English literature.", "She didn't ask experienced teachers for advice.", "She took too much time off to eat and sleep.", "She had blind trust in what she learnt at college."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2562, "question": "Black has long been praised for its ability to better women's figures and suit every occasion. But the color has a side-effect--it ages the face. While black does give the appearance of a slimmer figure by making the shadows less visible, wearing it next to the face brings out a negative effect. Black clothing can highlight dark lines under the chin, shadows around the eyes and wrinkles on the face. The effect can be as serious as making women feel exhausted, self-conscious and upset. Wrinkles and sunken areas appear deeper and more pronounced, meaning the effect is more obvious in older women. Dark scarves, hats and high-collared coats are apparently particularly likely to emphasize aging features of the face. But fear not. The effect can be _ by a splash of color around the neck--in the ...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["high-collared coats are not suitable for warm-skinned women", "a woman from eastern Asia may not look young with black against her face", "men with deep wrinkles would look unhealthy in black", "Joan Collins has a warm skin tone"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2572, "question": "The first reality TV show in the world was called Expedition Robinson and it was shown in Sweden in 1997. Half the population of the country watched the final event and a new kind of TV program was born. Two years later in Holland , the first series of Big Brother was filmed. Again, it was a great success and the final program was watched by 15 million people. Now more than 20 countries around the world have Big Brother or Expedition Robinson on their TV screens. The ordinary people who take part in the programs are known by millions of people in their own countries and reality TV has become big, big business. For the TV producers, reality TV is a dream come true because many of the programs cost nothing to make. At some point, the television viewers are asked to telephone the program to v...\n\nQ: Who would pay for the cost of the reality TV shows according to the passage?", "options": ["TV producers who make reality TV shows", "TV actors who take part in reality TV shows.", "TV viewers who telephone reality TV shows", "TV companies which broadcast reality TV shows"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 785, "question": "Wood Buffalo National Park Wood Buffalo National Park is Canada's largest national park and one of the largest in the world. Established in 1922 to protect the last remaining herds of bison in northern Canada, it now protects an outstanding example of Canada's Northern Boreal Plains. The park was designated a World Heritage Site in 1983. Phone: (780) 697-3662 E-mail: wbnp.info@pc.gc.ca Banff National Park of Canada Banff's rich history dates back to 1885, when three railway workers stumbled upon hot mineral springs surfacing from deep within the mountains. This discovery led to the establishment of Banff National Park, and marked the beginning of Canada's national park system. Spanning 6,641 meadows and rivers, Banff National Park is one of the world's premier destination spots. Phone: (40...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly taken from   _  .", "options": ["a travel guidebook", "a student's textbook", "a latest newspaper", "an entertaining book"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2516, "question": "The interview had been going on for about 20 minutes and everything seems to be going well. Then,suddenly,the interviewer asks an unexpected question,\"Which is more important,law or Dove?\" Job applicants in the West increasingly find themselves asked strange questions like this. And the signs are that this is beginning to happen in China. Employers want people skilled,enthusiastic and devoted. So these are the qualities that any reasonably intelligent job applicants will try to show no matter what his or her actual feelings are. In response,employers are increasingly using questions which try and show the applicant's true personality. The question in the first paragraph comes from a test called the Keirsey Personality Sorter. It is an attempt to discover how people solve problems,rather th...\n\nQ: From the passage we know that  _  .", "options": ["job applicants are always asked such questions", "more Chinese applicants fail to find a job", "applicants should not act as reasonably as a prisoner", "the aptitude test is becoming popular worldwide"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 711, "question": "Your Car Is Ready for Take-off The flying car has been talked about for many years,but now it appears that the idea is about to become a reality. An international company has built a two-seater plane that, at the touch of a button ,transforms into a car perfectly suitable for driving on public roads. It has been designed so that the wings fold up automatically; and it takes just 15 seconds to switch between flying and driving. With its wings fully open and the propeller spinning, it can take off from any airfield. Flying cars are quicker than traditional ones for travelling from city to city,and they can run on ordinary fuel. Another big advantage is that they are cool ,like something you would see in an action film. At the moment9however, the flying car's wheels are illegal to leave the g...\n\nQ: We know from the passage that the flying car  _", "options": ["has to run on special fuel", "will replace traditional planes", "is popular with the rich", "can shift between two forms"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2685, "question": "Silk production has a long and colourful history unknown to most people. Scientific discoveries have shown that silk production existed in China from around 2500 B.C., although it could be much older. For hundreds of years, China kept the secret of silk to itself as one for the most closely protected secrets in history. Anyone revealing the secret of silkworms or trying to take silkworm eggs out of ancient China was punished by death. At one time silk was reserved only for the Chinese emperor. Gradually, others began wearing silk. In addition to being used for clothing, silk came to have industrial uses in ancient China, something that happened in the West only in modern times. Silk was used to make musical instruments, fishing lines, weapons, ropes and even paper. During the Han Dynasty s...\n\nQ: How was China able to keep the secret of silk production?", "options": ["It refused to sell its silk to other countries.", "Foreigners were not permitted to enter China.", "The silkworms needed were not able to survive outside China.", "Chinese passing on the secret to foreigners were seriously punished."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1125, "question": "Father's Garden My father was always a good gardener. One of my earliest memories is standing without shoes in the freshly tilled soil, my hands blackened from digging in the ground. As a child, I loved following Dad around in the garden. I remember Dad pushing the tiller ahead in perfectly straight lines. Dad loved growing all sorts of things: yellow and green onions, watermelons almost as big as me, rows of yellow corn, and our favorite--- red tomatoes. As I grew into a teenager, I didn't get so excited about gardening with Dad. Instead of magical land of possibility, it had turned into some kind of prison. As Dad grew older, his love for gardening never disappeared. After all the kids were grown and had started families of their own, Dad turned to gardening like never before. Even when ...\n\nQ: When all the kids started their own families, the author's father   _  .", "options": ["stopped his gardening.", "turned to other hobbies.", "devoted more to gardening.", "focused on planting tomatoes."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 434, "question": "Health insurance can be very expensive. Some working people do not make enough money to pay for it. In the US there is a program called Healthy Families. This program offers people health insurance at a low cost. Families are charged about $7.00 a month for every child, and $10.00 for every adult. It costs much less than any other kind of health insurance. Having health insurance is very important. With this insurance, people can see a doctor when they are sick or hurt. The program is not expensive at all, but many people are still not enrolling in it. People say that it still costs too much money. They need all of their money to pay for things like food and rent . It would be great if everyone could have health insurance. People are working hard to come up with ways to make this happen. O...\n\nQ: In the passage we can learn all of the following EXCEPT that   _  .", "options": ["health insurance is very important for ordinary people", "people should make more money to pay for private health insurance", "the program is still too expensive for many people", "many people don't make enough money to pay for health insurance"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3087, "question": "Science isn't something mysterious, only for the few. Every one of us--whether a poet, worker, or physicist has to be able to think scientifically, and to understand some science, such as whether to smoke, what to eat, and what protection to use. Even for decisions that don't depend on some scientific facts, science remains the proven set of best methods for getting exact information about the world. Some people will end up as policy-makers in government or business. People such as these make decisions that affect the life of everyone, and most of them know no more about science than does the rest of the general public. Yet they are called upon to decide what to do about nuclear reactors , global warming, environmental toxins , expensive space programs, and biomedical research. It's nonsci...\n\nQ: The general public is required to   _  .", "options": ["support and understand the need of scientific education", "check what the scientists are saying", "give help to the policy-makers", "become professional scientists"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 335, "question": "Water is very important to living things. Without water there can be no life on the earth. All animals and plants need water. Man also needs water. We need water to drink, to cook our food and to clean ourselves. Water is needed in offices, factories and schools. Water is needed everywhere. There is water in seas, rivers and lakes. Water is found almost everywhere. Even in the desert part of the world, there is some water in the air. You can not see or feel it when it is a part of the air. The water in the seas, rivers and lakes is a liquid, the water in the air is a gas, and we call it water vapour . Clouds are made of water. They may be made of very small drops of water. They may also be made of snow crystals . Snow crystals are very very small crystals of ice. Ice is frozen water. It is...\n\nQ: We can drink water when it is  _", "options": ["a solid", "aliquid", "in the air", "turned into ice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1904, "question": "If you want to live longer and lower the risk of heart disease, a move to the mountains may help. Research by scientists in Greece shows that living in the mountains is good for the heart and longevity . People living at higher altitude have lower possibility of dying from heart disease than those closer to sea level, even if they have factors that could increase their risk. \"Residence in mountainous areas seems to have a 'protective effect' from heart disease,\" said Dr Nikos Baibas of the University of Athens. He and his colleagues suspect that the increased exercise from walking up mountainous area gives the heart a good workout and enables it to cope with lower levels of oxygen. Researchers studied the health records and death rates of 1,150 Greeks who lived in three villages near Athen...\n\nQ: The first sentence in the passage is used to   _  .", "options": ["give a very good guessing", "tell readers what the passage focuses on", "warn people of the risk of heart disease", "name a new unknown illness"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2791, "question": "It was 7:00 am in Kyoto, Japan, and the taxi company had just called a second time to say they couldn't find my house. Once again I spelt out directions even a blind person could follow. I glanced impatiently at my watch, and waited. Only two hours remained until my flight left--and it was an hour and a half trip to the airport. Outside, heavy rains were pouring down. My house was so far north in the city that buses pass only here times a day. The telephone rang again. \"Terribly sorry,\" began the man at the taxi company. Then I realized that the taxi company, flooded with calls, could only offer in-city runs. I had heard this happens when the weather gets bad. I shouted into the phone that I had a plane to catch and I would meet the taxi outside my house. Standing in the wind-driven rain, ...\n\nQ: Why did the writer call a taxi early in the morning?", "options": ["He wanted to catch a plane.", "He as unable to find the airport.", "There were few taxis in town.", "All the buses stopped because of the rain."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 159, "question": "Golf in the USA was until quite recently the hobby of old,middle class white men.Not any more.The fact that the class,age and race barriers that existed in the sport have finally been broken down is due almost entirely to two people.Tiger Woods and Michelle Wie. Tiger Woods was born in California in 1975 and is one of the greatest golfers of all time.His ethnic background is marvelously rich and varied.His father Earl was of mixed of black,Chinese and Native American ancestry and his mother Kultida,who was originally from Thailand,also had Chinese and Dutch forefathers. Woods became a professional golfer in 1996 and,less than a year later,astonished the world easily winning the prestigious Masters Colf Tournament,an annual event which takes place at the Augusta Golf Club in Georgia,USA.At ...\n\nQ: Which of the following sentences is true?", "options": ["Tiger Woods was of mixed black,Chinese,and Native America.", "Tiger Woods was not the first Asian American to win the Tournament.", "Tiger Woods'achievement was amazing because he was the youngest golfer.", "Tiger Woods'dramatic appearance on the golf scene had the attitude to this sport in USA changed."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3005, "question": "People bury treasure to stop other people from taking it. They choose a quiet place, dig a deep hole and bury the treasure in it. Then they make a map of where the treasure is or write down other clues that will help them or someone else to find it again. In Britain a few years ago, a writer wrote about some treasure that he had buried. He put clues in the story to help readers find it. Thousands of people hunted for the treasure. They dug holes all over Britain, hoping to find it. One of the most popular adventure stories ever written is Robert Louis Stephenson's \"Treasured Island\", an exciting story about a young boy, Jim Hawkins, who is captured by pirates and later finds some buried treasure. Then there is the true story about a man who had to travel overseas for a year. He did not tru...\n\nQ: The writer in Britain    _    .", "options": ["really had buried something.", "started a nationwide treasure hunt.", "had lost his treasure and wanted people to help him find it.", "caused trouble because people dug holes everywhere."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 870, "question": "To Whom It May Concern: prefix = st1 /Chengdu #7 High School is proud to send an Odyssey of the MindTeam to World Competition this year. They competed inShanghaifor the National Competition and were selected to go to World. The World Competition will be held at the University of Maryland in theUnited Statesat the end of May. Odyssey of the Mind is a creative problem-solving competition. Teams of up to seven students will solve a complex problem using innovative ideas and materials. They will be judged on originality in three separate categories. Odyssey of the Mind competitions emphasize team work and creative \"out of the box\" solutions. The strength of this program is that the solutions are the work of the students only - neither coaches nor parents are allowed input. During the competiti...\n\nQ: Odyssey of the Mind competitions aim to   _  .", "options": ["drive the students to work harder", "encourage students to find out solutions after class", "help the competitors to think \"outside the box\"", "help the competitors to go to a better university"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2620, "question": "In the dark and damp market,Chen ShuChu,near her sixties,owns a stall that her father left her.The stall,called YuanJin Vegetables,is her everything.Chen earns only a little money by selling vegetables,but she has donated about $321,550 to help poor children. In March,Forbes magazine named her one of the 48 great philanthropists from the AsiaPacific region.A month later,TIME magazine selected the year's top 100 influential people and Chen was one of them.Although she has received many honours and rewards,Chen only cares about her vegetable stall and whether her regular customers buy her vegetables or not.\"I do not place great importance on money.When I donate to help others,I feel happy and I can sleep well at night.\" Chen said. Chen's ability to donate such a great deal of money has led m...\n\nQ: From the text,we can learn that Chen is  _  .", "options": ["confident and kindhearted", "wealthy and simple", "hardworking and selfless", "proud and serious"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 647, "question": "I was dirty smelly hungry and some somewhere beneath all that, suntanned .It was the end of an Inter-Rail holiday.My body couldn't take any more punishment. My mind couldn't deal with any more foreign timetables, currencies or languages. \" _ ,\" I said, as I stepped onto home ground.I said exactly the same thing the following year.And the next, all I had to do was buy one train ticket and, because I was under twenty--five years old,I could spend a whole month going anywhere I wanted in Europe. Ordinary beds are never the same once you've learnt to sleep, in the passage of a train, the rhythm rocking you into a deep sleep. Carrying all your possessions on your back in a tucksack makes you have a vefy basic approach to travel,and encourages incredible wastefulness that can lead to burning soc...\n\nQ: At the end of his first trip, the writer said\"Never again\"because", "options": ["He fell ill", "he disliked trains", "he was tired from the journey", "he had lost money"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3148, "question": "Working Wives Last week, we published an article about modern marriage. A recent survey showed that in England 51 percent of married women go out to work . people were asked what they thought of \"working wives\". The results were as follow: Men Women In favor 70% 80% Against 10% 20% Don't know 20% 0% We asked readers to write and tell us their opinions. Here are some of the hundreds of letters we received. I'm a (woman)photographer. I make plenty of money, travel a lot, and meet a lot of people. I enjoy my work, and would hate to stay at home. I would never marry a man who wanted me to give up my work. Ms. Jojo O Leary Hampstead At present there are over 1,000,000 unemployed men in Britain. If a woman gets a job, she puts one more man out of work. Perhaps that man has a wife and twelve chil...\n\nQ: Ted Stubbs thought that women going out to work   _  .", "options": ["would make men lose chances for work", "would be better than men", "would weaken the right of the husband at home", "would be meaningless"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1185, "question": "A recent study, published in last week's Journal of the American Medical Association, offers a picture of how risky it is to get a lift from a teenage driver. Indeed, a 16-year-old driver with three or more passengers is three times as likely to have a deadly accident as a teenager driving alone, while the risk of death for drivers between 30 and 59 decreases with each additional passenger. The authors also found that the death rates for teenage drivers increased sharply after 10 p.m., and especially after midnight. With passengers in the car, the driver was even more likely to die in a late-night accident. Robert Foss, a scientist at the University of North Carolina Highway Safety Research Center, says the higher death rates for teenage drivers have less to do with \"really stupid behavior...\n\nQ: According to Robert Foss, the high death rate of teenage drivers is mainly because of   _  .", "options": ["their frequent driving at night", "their improper ways of driving", "their driving with passengers", "their lack of driving experience"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2083, "question": "Monkeys are very similar to us in many ways. We enjoy watching them because they often act like us. In fact, scientists say monkeys and humans share a common ancestor. Monkeys make us smile, too, because they are creatures full of playful tricks. This is why many monkey expressions are about tricky people or playful acts. One of these expressions is monkeyshines, meaning tricks or foolish acts. So, when a teacher says to a group of students: \"Stop those monkeyshines right now!\", you know that the kids are playing, instead of studying. You might hear that same teacher warn a student not to monkey around with a valuable piece of equipment. You monkey around with something when you are touching or playing with something you should leave alone. Also, you can monkey around when you feel like do...\n\nQ: If you drew a funny picture on your friend's face while he was sleeping, you were   _  .", "options": ["monkeying around", "doing money business", "enjoying a barrel of monkeys", "making a monkey out of him"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2610, "question": "Matt grow the best vegetables in the village.He grows fruit too--big , sweet apples and oranges.And what else ? Well , the biggest and the prettiest flowers.Things grow in Matt' s garden all through the year.He cuts some flowers for his sitting room table ; and of course , he eats some fruit and vegetables.But he sells everything else in the market.Matt is not a poor man. He knows a few other gardens ; but he does not have any friends.You might ask , \" What is that ? Why doesn ' t he have friends ? \" I will tell you.People do not understand him.And they do not understand his garden, \" Why not ? \" you will ask.\" It' s a very good garden , isn' t it ? \" It is a wonderful garden.Matt plants things in spring , summer and autumn and winter .After that he does very little work.He sits in the gar...\n\nQ: There are not only vegetables and flowers , but also    _    in Matt' s garden .", "options": ["plants", "fruit trees", "ants", "crops"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1799, "question": "Good state is when your body and mind are in the best condition for learning. These pages describe that state. Applying this information will increase your learning performance, without using any of the other techniques on this site. You will learn faster if your cells, body and mind are in good condition, or good \"state.\" Being in good state doesn't just increase your memory and learning performance. Being in good state also helps improve your health and well-being, with resulting benefits in many other areas of your life.The state described on these pages leads to peak condition for performing well in many human endeavors, from flying a plane to playing football. I've grouped the major contributors to Memletic State into three layers. These are the cell, physical and mental state layers....\n\nQ: The passage may be taken from  _  .", "options": ["a newspaper", "a magazine", "a website", "a notice"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 820, "question": "Long after the 1998 World Cup was won, disappointed fans were still cursing the disputed refereeing decisions that denied victory to their team. A researcher was appointed to study the performance of some top referees. The researcher organized an experimental tournament involving four youth teams. Each match lasted an hour, divided into three periods of 20 minutes during which different referees were in charge. Observers noted down the referees' errors, of which there were 61 over the tournament. Converted to a standard match of 90 minutes, each referee made almost 23 mistakes, a remarkably high number. The researcher then studied the videotapes to analyse the matches in detail. Surprisingly, he found that errors were more likely when the referees were close to the incident. When the offic...\n\nQ: The findings of the experiment show that   _  .", "options": ["errors are more likely when a referee keeps close to the ball", "the farther the referee is from the incident, the fewer the errors", "the more slowly the referee runs, the more likely errors will occur", "errors are less likely when a referee stays in one spot"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2040, "question": "When on vacation,what do you look for in a hotel?Maybe you want a comfortable bed, or a suitable place.However,if you want something out of the ordinary and wish to go beyond the mundane, these spectacular hotels offer a stay you won't soon forget! Hippo Point For those who prefer an overnight stay with some four-footed or two-winged guests, Hippo offers unique rooms on the East African plains .The nine-story tower is treated as one of the top 10 resorts in the world.Guests enjoy incredible views of Olodian Bay.More than 520 species of birds gather around the lake,their calls sounding in the air. Dog Bark Park Inn At the Dog Bark Park Inn,sleeping in a doghouse is a good thing! Located near Cottonwood,Idaho,this bed and breakfast is inside the world's largest dog. Guests relax on dog-theme...\n\nQ: If you go to Sala Silvermine, you will   _  .", "options": ["return to the ground after sleeping there.", "travel the deepest mine with a guide.", "go 155 meters underground all by yourself.", "experience the feeling of loneliness all day."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1873, "question": "When people talk about Golden Age in Leadville, Horace Austin Warner Tabor and his second wife, Elizabeth McCourt must be included. Their story is becoming one of the legends of the Old West. H.A.W.Tabor was a school teacher in Vermont. With his first wife and two children he left Vermont in 1855 to settle in Kansas. Perhaps he was attracted by rumors of fortunes to be made in Colorado mines. A few years later he moved west to the small Colorado mining camp known as California Gulch, which he later renamed Leadville when he became its leading citizen. \"Great deposits of lead are sure to be found here.\"he said. As it turned out, it was silver, not lead, that was to make Leadville's fortune and wealth. Tabor knew little about mining himself, so he opened a general store selling everything fr...\n\nQ: Tabor renamed the city Leadville when he became its first mayor because   _  .", "options": ["it was the mayor's duty to do so", "a great storage of lead was found there", "the city had brought great fortune to Tabor", "miners were eager to search for lead"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2202, "question": "'Well,' began Enfield, 'I was coming home about three o'clock on a black winter morning, when suddenly I saw two people. The first was a short man who was walking along the street, and the second was a little girl who was running as fast as she could. Well, the two bumped into each other and the child fell down. Then a terrible thing happened. The man calmly walked all over the child's body with his heavy boots, and left her screaming on the ground. It was an inhuman thing to do. I ran after the man, caught him and fetched him back. There was already a small crowd around the screaming child. The man was perfectly cool, but he gave me a very evil look, which made me feel sick in my stomach. The child's family then arrived, and also a doctor. The child had been sent to fetch the doctor for a...\n\nQ: Which of the following makes Enfield, the narrator of the story, puzzled most?", "options": ["The doctor's attitude towards the short man.", "The validity of the cheque accepted by the bank.", "The name on the cheque the short man produced.", "The short man's attitude towards what he had done."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2292, "question": "Recreational tree climbing is taking root in the ecotourism industry, and it's sending guys like Tim Kovar to far off reaches of the globe. Kovar, a tree-climbing instructor, recently returned to the U.S. from Brazil, where he spent time developing a tree-climbing operation thanks to the \"slow travel\" movement. Slow travel, is like the slow food movement, the practice of giving fast food in favor of homegrown cooking--the kind that takes hours to prepare and enjoy. Likewise, slow travel urges visitors to experience a place's natural surroundings and learn about the ecology in a way not afforded by extreme games. \"Tree climbing is a slow activity,\" says Kovar. \"It's not something you do quickly and then you're on to the next thing or event.\" There is no such thing as a quick climb, especial...\n\nQ: Brumbaugh kneels on the ground before climbing trees to   _  .", "options": ["beg for the safety of climbing", "Expect to climb faster than her husband", "Show respect for the tree", "ask for permission of her husband"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1345, "question": "Pleasant Goat, lazy Goat, Beautiful Goat and Slow Goat, which one is your favorite? The second movie of the Chinese cartoon series of Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf again achieved noticeable box office takings in china, earning more than 40 million yuan merely three days after its debut . Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf is no doubt the most successful\"China made\"cartoon series recently. It is shown on TV almost every day and its core product can be seen almost in every child's goods store. It is the Chinese Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck. The cartoon series is not only welcomed by children, but is also often discussed among adult audiences. Pleasant Goat is appreciated for his courage and wisdom. While Big Big Wolf is considered a model husband though he is usually the bad guy in the story, a...\n\nQ: according to the passage, we can infer that_.", "options": ["in 2010 we will see the second movie of Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf", "this cartoon is the most successful \"China made\"cartoon series", "all people like to see the movie", "in 2010 it's estimated that the cartoon will earn over 40 million yuan"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 166, "question": "If you had a strange sound in your ear, what would you do? One man in Wales who thought he had a fly in his ear called 999, the emergency services number in Britain. And so did a woman who was worried about her green potatoes. Could she make chips with them? Were they poisonous? She didn't hesitate about calling the local ambulance service to ask. According to a recent report, more than 31,000 non-urgent calls were made to the Welsh Ambulance Service in the last year. Inappropriate calls are a headache for health professionals everywhere. In the US, prank calls to 911 happen on a daily basis. Many callers use apps which hide their identity. But those who try to be funny shouldn't be surprised if the police _ . One man from Colorado was arrested for making more than 1,200 prank calls, accor...\n\nQ: What does the author intend to suggest in the text?", "options": ["Prank calls are usually easy to identify.", "Operators feel annoyed by strange callers.", "Prank calls may cause serious results.", "Prank callers should be punished by law."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 991, "question": "In the United States, the legal age to drink alcohol is twenty-one --- one of the highest in the world. Americans debate whether _ should be lowered, or whether young drinkers would only drink more. In parts of Europe, the legal drinking age for beer, and sometimes hard liquor, is sixteen. Yet France may raise the age limit for beer and wine sales to eighteen, the same as for hard liquor there. Rules on alcohol differ from college to college in the United States. Many schools require all first-year students to take an alcohol prevention and education program, often given online. Some have a \"zero tolerance\" policy where alcohol is banned from all buildings. Parents are informed of violations and students may be suspended . At the University of Virginia in Charlottesville, permission is nee...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Studying in the US", "Rules on Alcohol on Campus in the US", "Campus Life in the US", "Alcohol on Campus in the US"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 328, "question": "Struggling in the US? Move to China! I graduated from the university with a degree of civil engineering. It is a good field but my heart was not in it. I wanted to be an actor or work in the entertainment industry...living a creative life. My choice of civil engineering was really a mistake but I realized too late. As soon as I graduated, I moved straight to Los Angeles--the home of the film and television industry! For three years, I tried to get a job in that field. I often worked as an extra in movies and TV shows--standing in the background while actors are in the foreground. This was fun for a while, but I wanted a real acting job, where I was speaking! Sadly, in Los Angeles, there is too much competition. Every race and age is represented: old, young, black, white, Asian and thousand...\n\nQ: How can we describe the writer's attitude toward life?", "options": ["Practical", "Passive", "Disappointed", "Positive"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1098, "question": "College visits are important.Before you commit years of your life and money to a school, be sure you're choosing a place,\" that is a good match for your personality and interests.You can't get the \"feel' of a school from any guidebook, so be sure to visit the campus.Below are a few tips for getting the most out of your college visit. 1.Explore on your own Of course you should take the official campus tour, but be sure to allow time to hang around on your own. The trained tour guides will show you a school's selling points.But the 1dest and prettiest buildings don't give you the entire picture of a college.Try to walk the extra mile and get the complete picture of the campus. 2.Read the Bulletin Boards When you visit the student center, academic buildings and residence hall, take a few minu...\n\nQ: Where does the passage probably come from?", "options": ["A news report", "A tourist poster.", "An educational journal.", "A geographical magazine."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1321, "question": "Recently educators have been questioning \"prep school\" (=preparatory school) where barely literate high school athletes get their transcripts by taking courses occasionally and sometimes by taking no courses at all. The athletes then go on to famous sports universities, where they exhaust their playing years before landing back on the streets without job opportunity or college degrees. The prep school scheme was meant to avoid academic qualification rules for college athletes made years ago by the National Collegiate Athletic Association. The N.C.A.A., which was slow to recognize the seriousness of the problem, has finally adopted policies to root it out. But those policies will not do the job unless everyone is involved, including prep schools and college athletics departments that still ...\n\nQ: What might be the author's attitude towards the prep school scheme?", "options": ["The writer thinks it a chance for high school athletes to go to college.", "The writer thinks more practical measures are needed to break it.", "The writer remains neutral on this issue.", "The writer believes poor children will have little chance to go to college if prep school scheme is broken."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2017, "question": "The old lady was glad to be back at the block of flats where she lived. Her shopping had tired her and the basket had grown heavier with every step of the way home. In the lift her thoughts were on lunch and a good rest, but when she got out at her own floor, both were forgotten in her sudden discovery that her front door was open. She was thinking that she must tell her daily maid the next morning to lock the door, and then she remembered that she had gone shopping after the maid had left and she knew that she had turned both keys in their locks. She walked slowly into the hall and at once noticed that all the room doors were open, yet following her regular practice she had shut them before going out. Looking into the living room she saw a sight of confusion over by her writing desk. It w...\n\nQ: The first thing she wanted to do, after she was sure that the house was opened by someone, was   _  .", "options": ["force the burglars out", "look around the rooms for the thieves", "go to the doorman for help", "sit down for a cup of tea in order to calm down"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1776, "question": "Dear Santa Claus, My name is Amy. I am 9 years old. I have a problem at school. Can you help me, Santa? Kids laugh at me because of the way I walk and run and talk. I have cerebral palsy. I just want one day when no one laughs at me or makes fun of me. Love, Amy At radio station WJLT in Fort Wayne, Indiana, letters poured in for the Christmas Wish Contest. When Amy's letter arrived at the radio station, manager Lee Tobin read it carefully. He thought it would be good for the people in Fort Wayne to hear about this special third grader and her unusual wish. Mr. Tobin called up the local newspaper. The next day, a picture of Amy and her letter to Santa made the front page of the \"News Sentinel\". The story spread quickly. All across the country, newspapers and radio and television stations re...\n\nQ: We may infer from Amy's story that   _   .", "options": ["people are easy to turn their eyes to the disabled", "Amy will still be made fun of by others", "the news media played an important role in helping Amy", "there are few disabled people in Amy's country"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1176, "question": "Rising levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere are a major cause of climate change, and now a new study has confirmed that atmospheric CO2is also affecting the ocean chemistry and potentially harming sea life. Montana State University scientist Robert Dore has been researching the water in the Pacific Ocean for almost two decades. We've been going to the same spot in the Pacific Ocean, and we try and characterize long-term change in the open ocean environment. And one of the key things that we measure is CO2levels. And we've been able to record this increasing quantity of atmospheric CO2into the ocean. Scientists expected that as atmospheric CO2increased, more and more of the carbon dioxide would be absorbed into the ocean, affecting the chemical balance of the sea water, with a potenti...\n\nQ: Scientist Robert Dore came to the conclusion based on  _  .", "options": ["his research and analysis", "the expectation of other scientists", "some former theory", "a major cause of climate change"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3294, "question": "Active vacations are often the most relaxing of all. But Wait! It's all in defining what an active vacation is. We don't expect you to take up jogging, backpacking, or hang gliding. we ask the sedentary vacationers to spend two to four hours a day doing things, such as walking the city streets, exploring a nature preserve, or taking a leisurely rowboat ride. These kinds of activities aren't just good for your physical health. They improve your mental health, even your spiritual health. And they make vacations memorable and worthwhile. Here are some fresh ideas for active and healthy vacation. Make the morning your activity time. At that time it is most likely that the weather will be friendlier, your energy level higher, and your schedule emptier than later in the day. Have a walk at dawn ...\n\nQ: How many tips does the writer give in the passage?", "options": ["Three", "Four", "Five", "Six"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 28, "question": "My favourite book is The Adventure of Tom Sawyer by Mark Twain.Tom lives with his aunt Polly in a quiet street of St. Petersburg, Missouri.He's a lively and clever young boy,and he finds himself in many exciting adventures.He runs away with his two friends,Huck Finn and Joe,to an island in the middle of the Mississippi River for several days.With Huck he goes looking for treasure, with Becky he gets lost in a cave.and finally,they find a box of gold. My favourite scene in the book is when everyone thinks Tom is dead.He decides to go to his own funeral.He hides and watches for a time and then suddenly he appears. Everyone is astonished to see him but they're also pleased to see him alive. Tom is the hero of the story,but there are other important characters.Huck is an outsider and everyone ...\n\nQ: .How did people feel when Tom appeared at his own funeral ?", "options": ["They were surprised and happy.", "They were surprised and sad", "They were worried and excited.", "They were frightened and happy."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2674, "question": "Science Fiction The science fiction type of entertainment is considered by most to be fathered by Jules Verne (A Journey to the Center of the Earth and Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea) and H. G. Wells (The Time Machine and The War of the Worlds). Sci-Fi, as it is commonly shortened, is a fictional story in which science and technology have a significant influence on the characters and plot. Many such works are guesswork about what the future holds and how scientific findings and technological advances will shape humankind. Writing in the late 1800s, Jules Verne was remarkably successful in his 10 guesses about future technologies of air conditioning, automobiles, the Internet, television, and underwater, air, and space travel. Unbelievably, of all places from which to choose, Jules V...\n\nQ: What can science fiction offer to people?", "options": ["A forecast of how a new discovery could influence mankind.", "A thoughtful look at the present drawbacks of technology.", "An analysis of why a new technology could be used to harm human.", "A thoughtful look at the past and what brought us to this point in history."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3420, "question": "Hello-Hello, a creative mobile language learning company, announced the launch of Hello-Hello World, a free application for the iPad that helps people learn a new language by connecting them with native speakers through social networking. The application lets users complete language lessons and connect with Hello-Hello's global community of language learners with members in almost 100 countries to help each other in the learning process. Hello-Hello World is available in 11 different languages and allows users to submit both oral and writing exercises for their friends and Hello-Hello's language experts to review. Users are also able to provide written feedback on their friend's exercises directly from their mobile devices. \"The most effective way to learn a new language is through total i...\n\nQ: With the launch of Hello-Hello world, users can   _  .", "options": ["talk to any foreigners in the world", "speak any foreign languages fluently", "practice pronouncing words correctly", "communicate with native speakers anytime"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3176, "question": "Juac has made the leap from being an African refugee to a chess champion in the United States. His job is to share his expertise with students in schools, chess camps and other events. During Sudan's civil war in the mid-1980s, Juac was forced out of the country with 20,000 0ther so -called Lost Boys. He fled to Ethiopia, then to Kenya staying in a refugee camp for eight years, where he learned to play chess. Juac described a dangerous journey in which half the boys didn't survive. To eat, they had to kill wild animals. \"There were animals on the way. It was about a thousand miles and sometimes there was no water. When we were in Ethiopia, we had to cross the river and there a lot drowned.\" Juac arrived in the United States in 2004 and began working as a security guard. Winning a chess tou...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that Juac   _", "options": ["must be teaching kids chess for free", "is patient and good at math problems", "surely has his own chess school in American", "hasn't taken part in international chess contests"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 778, "question": "The Pew report,which was based on surveys carried out in Britain,France,Germany, Italy,Spain,Greece, Poland and the Czech Republic,said that the European Union was \"the new sick man of Europe\".The percentage of Europeans with a good view of the EU has fallen from 60 percent last year to 45 percent now. The UK may be considered the most Eurosceptic country ,but its support for the Union has barely changed in the past 1 2 months,falling only two points to 43 percent.But,France's backing for the EU has fallen sharply,from 60 percent last year to 41 percent today. On the question of whether to remain in the EU, 46 percent of the British want to leave the Union and surprisingly,the same percentage want to stay. The Pew report's authors said, \"The long-term economic crisis has created bad forces...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE of the recent Pew report?", "options": ["The UK has the smallest number of people against the EU.", "There's a slight change of the UK's supporting for the EU.", "More than half of the Germans raise questions about the EU.", "A large number of French people are in favor of the EU."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3275, "question": "Throughout life,change is the only thing that seems constant.Change has come to my 1ife many ways,in myself,and in my surroundings.At the same time,some things stay the same.This is when traditions are formed.I am often reminded of this by the photograph that sits by my bed. It all began with a kiss on my very first day of school.I remember dancing around the mirror,watching as my dark blue dress created a teacup around my waist.I admired the little ruffle of my shirt collar and how it matched perfectly with the trim at the bottom of my dress.I knew I would be the envy of all my classmates. But somehow,something was missing.I reached under my bed for the large box of bows ,in every color1 imaginable,that I was famous for.I picked out a white one that would match my shirt and carefully ran ...\n\nQ: What's the author's family tradition?", "options": ["Photographs must be put in bedroom.", "Taking family pictures on a child's first day of school.", "Dad always drove children to their school.", "Each girl of the family has a large box of bows."], "answer": 1}]